<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">SFDC2SAP-product-broadcast</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
This Anypoint Template should serve as a foundation for setting an online sync of products/materials from Salesforce to SAP.
Everytime there is a new product or a change in already existing one in Salesforce instance, the template will fetch it and upsert it in SAP.
			
Requirements have been set not only to be used as examples, but also to establish a starting point to adapt your integration to your requirements.
			
As implemented, this Anypoint Template leverage the [Batch Module](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing).
The batch job is divided into *Input*, *Process* and *On Complete* stages.
The integration is triggered by poll to Salesforce products. New or modified products with non-empty product code are passed to the batch as input.
In the batch the material is fetched from SAP by its `ProductCode`. Depending on the result, the product is then created or updated in SAP.
Finally during the *On Complete* stage the Anypoint Template will log output statistics data into the console.
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_studio">
		<![CDATA[
In order to make this Anypoint Template run on Anypoint Studio there are a few extra steps that need to be made.
Please check this Documentation Page:

+ [Enabling Your Studio Project for SAP](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/SAP+Connector#SAPConnector-EnablingYourStudioProjectforSAP)
		]]>
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
		<![CDATA[
To make this Anypoint Template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered. All of them deal with the preparations in both, that must be made in order for all to run smoothly.
**Failling to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**

Before continue with the use of this Anypoint Template, you may want to check out this [Documentation Page](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/SAP+Connector#SAPConnector-EnablingYourStudioProjectforSAP), that will teach you how to work 
with SAP and Anypoint Studio.

## Disclaimer

This Anypoint template uses a few private Maven dependencies in oder to work. If you intend to run this template with Maven support, please continue reading.

You will find that there are three dependencies in the pom.xml file that begin with the following group id: 
	**com.sap.conn.jco** 
These dependencies are private for Mulesoft and will cause you application not to build from a Maven command line. You need to replace them with "provided" scope and copy the libraries into the build path.
		]]>
		</section>
		<section id="sap_dst">
<![CDATA[
This template uses custom BAPI functions. To create them please use following steps:

1. Create structure `ZMMST_ENH_MARA` in transaction `SE11` as per its definition in file `structure_ZMMST_ENH_MARA.abap`
2. Create table type `ZMMTTY_ENH_MARA` in transaction `SE11` as per its definition in file `table_type_ZMMTTY_ENH_MARA.abap`
3. Create message class called `ZMULESOFTINTEGRATION` in transaction `SE91` as per definition in file `msg_class_ZMULESOFTINTEGRATION.abap`
4. Create function module `ZMMFM_MATERIAL_GETLIST` in transaction `SE37` as per source file `ZMMFM_MATERIAL_GETLIST.abap`

Referenced files are in [src/main/resources] directory.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
Salesforce imposes limits on the number of API Calls that can be made. However, in this template, only one call per poll cycle is done to retrieve all the information required.		
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		<![CDATA[
**Common configuration**

+ poll.frequencyMillis `10000`
+ poll.startDelayMillis `5000`
+ page.size `100`
+ watermark.default.expression `2015-09-11T12:30:00.000Z`
		
**SalesForce Connector configuration**

+ sfdc.username `bob.dylan@sfdc`
+ sfdc.password `DylanPassword123`
+ sfdc.securityToken `avsfwCUl7apQs56Xq2AKi3X`
+ sfdc.url `https://test.salesforce.com/services/Soap/u/32.0`

**SAP Connector configuration**

+ sap.jco.ashost `your.sap.address.com`
+ sap.jco.user `SAP_USER`
+ sap.jco.passwd `SAP_PASS`
+ sap.jco.sysnr `14`
+ sap.jco.client `800`
+ sap.jco.lang `EN`

**SAP Material properties configuration**

+ sap.material.type `ZHTI`
+ sap.material.industrySector `T`
+ sap.material.baseUnitOfMeasurement `KGS`
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>